<page>
<pageurl>https://job-openings.monster.co.uk/Marketing-Intern-8690-London-UK-Broadgate-Estates/31/c36c7414-7e3a-43bc-8a82-583af4ddba47</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>eb1baf6b11b20f1664dabc660574b5ac</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2018-06-22 22:50:37 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <url>https://job-openings.monster.co.uk/Marketing-Intern-8690-London-UK-Broadgate-Estates/31/c36c7414-7e3a-43bc-8a82-583af4ddba47</url>
      <job_title>Marketing Intern (8690)</job_title>
      <category>communications</category>
      <company_name>Broadgate Estates</company_name>
      <city>London</city>
      <post_date>2018-05-19</post_date>
      <job_description>At British Land we manage, develop and finance a portfolio of high quality properties. We are a FTSE100 company structured as a Real Estate Investment Trust. Places People Prefer is at the heart of what we do, we create outstanding places that make a positive difference to people’s everyday lives. We are proud of the scale of our portfolio: Nearly 100,000 people live or work in our properties. They are visited around 350 million times each year and over 1,000 different organisations have chosen of our properties as their home. We have £19.1bn assets under management of which we own £13.9bn; our portfolio includes UK retail, Central London offices and prime residential. We have a small head office of around 250 people and outsource many aspects of our business; the size of our team encourages increased responsibility and entrepreneurialism.Role TitleMarketing InternLocationMarble Arch, LondonDivisionMarketingReporting toSenior Marketing Acquisition ManagerOur Offices &amp;amp; Residential portfolio is focused on London, reflecting its position as a leading global city – a place to live, work and do business. We provide a range of working and living space across our campuses atBroadgate,Regent’s PlaceandPaddington Central, as well as at distinctive standalone properties such asThe Leadenhall Building, which all combine a broad mix of retail and leisure.The offices and residential marketing team are responsible for the creation and implementation of the marketing strategy of the London office and residential portfolio. This ranges from taking newly developed buildings to market through to enlivening our campuses with events and activities for our tenants.The RoleA new and exciting position for a university graduate with an interest in a marketing career to join a fast paced FTSE 100 company. The Marketing Intern will provide full support to the Customer Marketing team in the implementation of its marketing strategy.Key ResponsibilitiesUpdating brochure and website contentEnsure all templates and guidelines are in place and complied withWork closely with marketing agencies to ensure implementation of marketing strategyLiaise with all levels within the companyMonthly traffic analysis and dashboard reportsFormatting, sending and creating of HTML (email) newslettersSupport team in physical marketing mail outsSupport team at planning and delivery of launch events and customer eventsEditing and proof reading reports, documents, letters and PowerPoint presentationsPreparing weekly content for internal communicationsWriting briefs and project managementResearch topic per quarter and present back to the team.RequirementsMust have a strong interest to pursue a career in marketingExcellent organisational and communication skillsWorks well under pressure and remains calm at all timesWill be a confident, pro-active, self-starting and highly professional individualMust have advanced knowledge of MS Word, Outlook, PowerPoint and intermediate knowledge of ExcelAbility to prioritise work with competing deadlines in order to respond to the changing internal environmentA proactive approach to improvements; such as suggesting ideas and being open minded to the ideas of othersMust be able to accept and act on feedbackMust have an excellent attention to detail and accuracyMust be able to use own initiativePlease note that we endeavour to get back to all applicants within 28 days. If you haven’t heard from us within this period, please assume that you have been unsuccessful on this occasion.</job_description>
      <company_description> About this company Broadgate Estates </company_description>
      <job_board>monster</job_board>
      <geo>uk</geo>
      <location>NA</location>
</record>
</page>